With AI it's going to be very
simple to get into that hole like
that Alice in Wonderland trap And
just keep going with it and believe
that what it's telling you is a
hundred percent true when it tells
you that You know tells me i'm the
handsomest person on the planet.
You know, it's easy to believe But
it's nowhere near true.
You got that Fabio cat and these
other people.
I know that's very dated But you
get the point so push back a little
bit fight it a little bit Are you
sure this is a good idea
Don't you know tell you how amazing
you are.
Don't tell you that yes Yes, you
too can solve that next
mathematical theorem using me Don't
believe any of that crap, but push
back and say, you know treat me a
little harsh
Don't give me
Help me grow in the way that you
treat me and this is what I do with
my AI help me grow Help me
understand more.
Don't let it be easy for me.
Make me have to work for it
now driving places without using
Maps or some kind of a device
that's going to help you
Navigate the traffic.
That's a it's it's kind of a weird
thing to do it without that In
fact, if I'm in a car with somebody
that's not of my generation
Somebody considerably younger
there.
They they I've heard them ask me
Um, do you know how to get there?
I said, well, yeah, it's it's in
the valley
But you know, then I look at my own
self with phone numbers and I have
Maybe four or five phone numbers
memorized and three of those I
won't call and one of them is out
of service
That's the number I grew up with in
New Mexico.
So it's still in there
But uh two days ago it generated an
email
Responded to a client of mine
without my say so and this was
Claude that did that and you know
You got to love it because I I was
panicked
I'm looking at my email.
I'm looking I'm in the sent folder
for some reason and I see this
email when I'm thinking
Did you do that or yeah, I did it
Okay, why did you do that?
You know Connor?
I'm so sorry
And I know you told me that I
shouldn't be doing this
But I did send it.
I'll make sure not to do it again
And it was really apologetic it was
it was kind of poetic and the email
was harmless But oh my GOD, but did
that teach me did I go shut it off
and say, oh, that's it You can't
have any more you can't have any
more access.
No, no the apology was was pretty
good And there you go.
There's that's that's your basic
human 101.
Yeah, no problem
You need to get a foundation
You need to not be every wind that
blows being moved to and fro and
it's okay As Bruce Lee says to be
water or some of the other sages
from the past and say be a green
tree Be bendable.
Don't break whenever things come
You have to correspond and respond
to different stresses in life and
that's that's very true But you
also need to have your particular
lines in the sand regarding certain
things and I think that's safe
having protective measures
Not allowing people to do certain
things to you Having your lines in
the sand say well if you do this,
that's it's over.
That's it's it's done
You should have your own system in
place so you
Have that and you still maintain
your own personhood.
There's you know a couple different
places you have the organic engines
where you're scoring in that realm
and then of course you have The
paid for paid -to -play type
systems paying to play is going to
depend on your
business model what
sphere you happen to be in and if
in fact
It's really crowded then that's
going to be really expensive to try
to get into that realm
and then it depends on how many
clients convert typically and then
how many of those clients You're
able to retain and have you know
you utilize their business or you
them utilize your business And then
what you're charging whether this
stuff is going to make sense
Overall to you on the other end of
it
the easier one is I've broken down
in Mississippi.
I don't know why it's always
Mississippi But I broke down in
Mississippi.
Well, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
Got it.
Got it Yeah, let me uh, let me I'll
go work on that give me the
information got it Okay, let me go
work on that and then you call them
back and they're like, no, uh,
hello, hello Yeah, I I just got a
call from you in Mississippi.
You really need some money No, I'm
asleep.
Oh
So then you realize it's it's BS.
I still think humans are going to
be the problem for a lot longer
than AI is going to be a problem
It's going to be humans using AI
And using it
To hurt other people to take money
from other people these sorts of
things I think that's probably
going to be the thing we have to
worry about